{
    "subject": "resource/Easton_Corbin",
    "predicate": "ontology/hometown",
    "object": "resource/United_States",
    "human_readable": "Easton Corbin's hometown is United States.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.988455057144165,
            "question": "Is the United States considered Easton Corbin's hometown?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9375419616699219,
            "question": "Easton Corbin's hometown is in which nation?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.921574592590332,
            "question": "Is Easton Corbin originally from the United States?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9060003161430359,
            "question": "What country is Easton Corbin's hometown in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8701311349868774,
            "question": "Is Easton Corbin a US native?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7622363567352295,
            "question": "Where is Easton Corbin from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6176015734672546,
            "question": "Where did Easton Corbin grow up?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6164583563804626,
            "question": "What is the nationality of Easton Corbin?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4429767429828644,
            "question": "Can you tell me Easton Corbin's birthplace?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.426757276058197,
            "question": "Where did Easton Corbin call home?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Easton Corbin's hometown is United States.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8874_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me Easton Corbin's birthplace?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8874_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the nationality of Easton Corbin?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8874_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where did Easton Corbin grow up?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8874_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8874_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8874_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8874_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8874_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8874_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8874_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8874_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8874_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8874_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8874_77.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents state that Easton Corbin was born in Trenton, Florida, and lived on his grandparents' farm following his parents' divorce. Florida is a state within the United States, so it supports the statement that Easton Corbin's hometown is in the United States."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "Multiple pieces of text state he is from Florida and even mention his hometown, Trenton, Florida.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}